CJ ENTERTAINMENT PRESENTS
A BIDANGIL PICTURES PRODUCTION
SONG JOONG-KI
PARK BO- YOUNG
EXECUTIVE PRODUCER
JEONG TAE-SUNG
How hideous...
A WEREWOLF BOY
Turn off the TV.
It's distracting
I'm watching it
Any news from Eun-ju?
She called yesterday
She says she misses you
She couldn't tell me herself?
It's nighttime here
when she calls
I suspect she has a new boyfriend
What? In Korea?
You should've kept your eye on her
Good God,
listen to yourselves
She's 19
She's supposed he dating
Hello?
Yes
Does Mrs. Kim Suni live there?
That's right
May I speak to her, please?
One moment, please
Gran, there is a call
for you from Korea
It must he Eun-ju
Hi, sweetheart!
Are you Mrs. Kim Suni?
This is she
I see...
Thank you
Who was it?
What's it about?
I need to go to Korea
PRODUCED BY
KIM SUJIN, YUN IN-BEOM
WRITTEN AND DIRECTED BY
JO SUNG-HEE
Gran!
Can you believe
I got a C on my midterm?
My professors use such posh language
they don't even sound Korean
The key is to doing it over and over
That's how you learn anything
- Hello?
- Hi, mom
- Did you meet her?
- We're in the car right now
Where abouts are you?
Gangwon-do, Hwacheon-gun,
Do...gae...
- Where is that?
- Dogye...
Put gran on the phone
Okay.
Gran?
Hi, it's me
I had a good flight, ate well,
and I didn't forget my pills
You should've let Eun-ju
take care of it
It's no trouble
Just make the sale
and come right home
Is this where you used to live?
Yeah, only briefly
It looks kind of creepy now
Like a haunted house
A haunted house?
It was like that even hack then
A place fit for a monster
How old were you?
When I was about your age
When I was as pretty as you
Back then...
47 years ago
Quiet!
I feel terrible
for troubling you like this
- It's no trouble
- Thank you so much
Thank you
Get out of the way, Suni
You must he the younger one
Put that down, sweetheart
You should get some rest
I'm all right
Just that one, then
Oh dear, that's a heavy one
Neighbors should look out
for each other
It's only right
Stop running around, Dong-seok
You'll break that
What a nice house!
Hey, come and give us a hand here
Let me get that
Please don't mind him
What do you think? Plenty of fresh air,
the house isn't all that had either
My summer house is in the area, too
The fence was too high,
so I got rid of it
Thank you
I'm forever in debt...
- Stop it, mom
- What's the matter?
That's my hall
- Careful
- Look! A pig bladder
Why won't you go inside, Suni?
If it wasn't for you,
it would've taken us an eternity
- Don't mention it
- Please help yourselves
Sweethearts, did you say 'thank you'?
- Thank you
Dong-seok and Dong-mi,
did you thank Mrs. Kim for the food?
- Thank you
Half way through the meal?
Mr. Kim is out of town?
He passed away 2 years ago
I do a little proofreading to
look after the girls
I should invite the rest of the neighbors over
to say hello
But this is the whole village
It's just us and Dong-seok's
And there is a woman who lives with us
hut we rarely see her
I've been here for 5 years
and this is the first time
I've been inside this house
How many bedrooms are there?
You have a telephone, too
No-one lived here before us?
Well,
there was this man
hut we never got to know him
He pretty much kept to himself
Hardly ever spoke at all
And then...
Sweetie, can I have some more soup?
Then, he died of a heart attack
Left undiscovered for a while, too
In the barn outside, he kept
coyotes or wolves of some sort
Wow!
Why would he...?
For the meat?
No, I think he did
some kind of study on them
He would walk around with big books
What gorgeous girls you have!
Schools are quite far away though
The little one will go to Taeryeong Elementary
and the older one...
Jeonghwa Girls' High School, right?
Suni doesn't go to school
I'm sorry I didn't prepare much
How is it?
Please, we have plenty more food
I'm gonna get something from the yard
It's chilly out
Don't he too long
We can't really afford this big place
hut we had to move for Suni
Her doctor insisted
What's wrong with her?
It's her lungs
She studies at home for her diploma
I can't remember the last time
I saw a smile on her face
She has no friends, either
Honey...
Poor little thing...
No wonder she is as pale as a ghost
That's no big deal
I haven't set foot in a school my whole life
Who was that slimeball from earlier?
He is the son of my late
husband’s business partner
- So, not one of yours?
- No
I knew it!
He looked like a nasty man
Watching old people work
with his hands in his pockets
What was the slimeball doing here?
It was the slimeball
that got us this place
Only two other families in the entire village!
They seem nice though
I'll leave the window open
and get the furnace running
Your medicine?
Just took it
- How's the smell?
- Awful
- Dust?
- I don't know
Tomorrow, I'll give the place
a thorough scrub down
Get some rest
I think I will, darling
Moonlight Melancholy
Do not touch! - Kim Suni
Dark shadow inside meaningless being
Rot away and perish
Drop dead, useless invalid!
Wake up!
There is something outside
Wake up, Sun-ja
Mom, Suni won't leave me alone!
Good Lord!
Suni? Was that you?
Where did that come from?
Where is your sister?
In there, mom
- Oh my God, what happened?
- Why didn't you wake me?
What were you doing out?
Are you hurt? Here?
How horrifying!
You should've called me
Must have been a stray wolf
Is she okay?
Just a scratch
- I boiled some potatoes this morning
- Oh, you shouldn't have!
I'm sure it won't come hack
Have a good day
Leave that, honey
I'd rather you do some studying
and get your diploma,
if you want to go to America
Mom...?
Yes?
Look
What's that?
Good Lord! Mr. Jeong!
Stay still
Is that what you saw last night?
It could he. I'm not sure
Go away
Shoo! Shoo!
Come here
Come on out, come on
It's a human
Who are you?
You want this?
Mom!
Okay... Here, take it
What's this smell?
You want more? Yes?
What are you doing, mom?
Just tell him to go away
It's okay, sweetheart
Why isn't he going?
He can't talk?
I think he understands though
He is just some tramp
Just shoo him away
Name unknown, age undetermined...
Damn!
Do you have a pencil sharpener?
What are you going to do about him?
To he honest,
there isn't much we can do
They say there are 60,000 children
orphaned by the war
He looks about 17 or 18
Orphanages won't take in
adolescents like him
Is that a cut on his face?
Jeez! What's wrong with him?
Was he abused as a child?
Shouldn't you take him in
and look into the matter?
That's our job all right hut
my captain will blow his lid
Just throw him out
I'll see what I can do
Can you look after him in the mean while?
Why should I?
Like I said, there are
some 60,000 war orphans
A copy of application form,
3 copies of residence certificate,
- a copy of income certificate,
- Sorry, can you slow down?
certificate of taxation,
certificate for a surrender of guardianship,
status report on the child under your care
But I'm not his guardian...
- Then, you should've gone to the police
- The police sent me here
Just say you're the guardian
and declare surrender of custody
Why would he go to an orphanage
if he has a guardian?
Lady, we're going around in circles
Then of course, there is an easier way
What's that?
How much did you pay him?
Five hundred dollars
Five hundred dollars?
What a thief!
We'll have to get him cleaned first
...and rush their ambition
to communize the world
In his keynote speech, the director of
Central Intelligence Agency announced
the launch of Anti-communism Center
Forget your dreams
of taking over the world
What the heck?
Sweetie, can you find
some of dad's old clothes?
You, come with me
Hey! What are you doing?
That's for your hath. Don't drink that
Stop growling and take off your clothes
Come on
What an awful smell!
You are not a child
I shouldn't have to do this for you
At least you have the decency
to hold onto your pants
I'll scrub your hack
hut the rest is up to you
Are you asleep?
- Where's mom?
- What a stench!
Hey, come on!
Come and have your supper
Food, over there
Oh, dear...
What's wrong with him?
- The poor thing must've starved...
- What are you gonna do about him?
I talked to the county office today
They'll get in touch soon
And until then?
The officer has a lot of connections
It shouldn't take long
How about we take care of him till then?
What?
Only for a few days
Can't just ignore him now
Sweetheart, I promise you
Be a good boy
and get some sleep, all right?
Stop making funny noises
You shouldn't do that at night
Come down
Dog training manual
How long is this unpacking
going to take?
Honey, it'll spoil your appetite
I'm not eating with him
I'm going to the post office
Are you going hack to studying
any time soon?
I'm trying to find my hooks
Where are they?
Go away
Get away from me!
Don't you come any closer
Hey!
Mom!
Do you want this?
Anybody home?
You're still unpacking?
This is why you need a man
in the house
Move over
How come you're still unpacked
with 3 women in the house?
What's that thing still doing here
Please leave
I have to study
Why would you need a diploma
when all you gotta know is
how to cook a nice dinner for me?
- Don't touch me
- Don't he like that
I'm going to Seoul for a few days
How about a proper good bye?
What the fuck?
Jeez!
You...
Creep!
Thanks
- I can't get to the food
- Work your way around
Hey, that's my rice!
Will you calm down a little?
Dog training manual
Do you know where he is?
Who, Cheol-su?
Cheol-su?
I decided to call him that for now
Your father wanted that name for a son,
If we ever had a boy
Then, Sun-ja arrived and
I felt guilty even if it wasn't my fault
So, where is he?
Sun-ja took him outside
Can you believe that girl?
We've only just moved in
and she's made friends with everyone
Dong-seok!
Wait for me
You suck
No, I don't
I'll tell grandma that you left me out
We'll let her have a go after this
Okay
Home run!
No, that was a two-base hit
Dong-mi, you're up next
Then, Cheol-su
- Where did he go?
- Over there
Cheol-su!
Wow, he is fast
Throw me the hall
Throw it hard
Come on
You can't throw it like that
Stupid Cheol-su
Guys!
Why won't you answer me?
Oh God...
Didn't you hear me?
What have you got in your pocket?
Cheol-su, when I say 'wait,'
don't eat
hut wait, okay?
Here, w...
...wait
What is she doing?
Let's go see the goats
- Goats?
- Yeah, they eat paper
When I say 'wait,' don't eat!
You should wait
Don't... eat, got it?
One more time
I said 'wait,' you idiot!
What?
What are you gonna do?
No! Hey! No!
Wait! No. Wait!
Wait!
See what you have done?
You did good though
You wait like that, okay?
Now, when I say 'eat,' you eat
When I say 'eat,' eat like this
Here
Here we go
Wait
Not yet...
Good...
That's a good boy
Now ready?
Eat
I said 'eat'!
When I say 'eat,' you eat like this
Hold still
I'm supposed to do this
Good job, Cheol-su
I'm not doing this because I like you
I'm trying to work out a way
to eat with you
Now, one more time
Who put this behind the wardrobe?
Was it you?
Don't know
I thought you weren't eating with him
It's all right. Call him
Dong-mi? Dong-seok?
Guard your plates
Wait
Eat
Eat. Little at a time
There's a good boy
What? Let's eat
...I fall into endless bottom
Death. Despair
No!
Wait, you naughty boy!
Wait!
Well done, Cheol-su
Now spit out like this
Fold it like this
You see?
Put it in the wardrobe
Good job, Cheol-su
...and tie the two ends
You're doing good
Sun-ja can't do this yet
You learn fast
Sure
When did you last cut your hair?
Are you asleep?
We're going to the market
Get ready
But I'm not done
He looks great
Get ready now
Cheol-su, we'll he hack real soon
There are some chestnuts in the kitchen
No, wait...
- Mom, can he come with us?
- If you want
Come on
Why are you wearing your slippers?
Put on some proper shoes. Hurry!
What a tomboy!
Move over
I'm going! Chop, chop
Cheol-su! Your sweater!
Can I get some candy?
No. It's had for your teeth
How about this, then?
Somebody please cover her eyes
Are you getting me new trainers?
No, something for Cheol-su
What do you think of these?
Seriously?
- They're old men's pants
- Cheol-su, darling?
What do you think?
Nice, huh?
Where did he go?
He was right behind us
- Cheol-su!
Cheol-su!
Kim Cheol-su!
Where did he go?
He's over there
- Get your mom
- But I've got money
There you go
And one for the little one here
Hey, what are you doing?
You gotta pay before you eat!
He'll pay
What are you yelling at him for?
He's your son
I want one, too
Can we get two more?
Go on, children
You have beautiful kids
I have two girls and a boy, myself
Darling, you gotta chew your food
- Here you go
- Thank you
Don't take off like that again
Are you listening to me?
You shouldn't wander off like that
I think he should see a doctor
He's gone a little red and
got a few scratches
Is this the only medical facility around here?
I think I should take him to a real hospital
You see, this huge iron beam fell
on top of him
Get out
- Oh, I didn't mean ...
- Get out
I'm so sorry, I didn't mean any disrespect
It just came out wrong
Sit down
A real hospital?
And I'm a fraud?
I run a good practice
I've been serving this community
for over 30...
for 30 whole years...
Is it had?
Take him to a bigger hospital some time
This is called caramel
We have more hut
have to wait till tomorrow
Will you give us more tomorrow?
Sure
- We have dried persimmon at home
- What's that?
- You don't know what dried persimmon is?
- What is it?
Dried persimmon is dried persimmon
Suni, are you coming with us?
You're such a bother!
Where are you going?
To see the goats
They look real scary
- What's your 100 meter record?
- 20 seconds
Cheol-su!
This is for you
It's a beanstalk
Give it water and it'll grow bigger
- I can easily heat you
- Yeah, right
You'll get in trouble for that
It's okay. It's a used one
Get your own!
That's not it. Look
No, it's like this
- Right, sis?
- What?
You try
Try what?
Come on
To me it sounds more like...
Don't laugh
Mr. Jeong is coming
Hey, were you laughing?
What's so funny?
You try it then
Come on! Try!
Chul-soo, what's with you!
Be quiet!
What are you guys doing here?
You kids fed papers again!
- Guys! Run!
- Run!
Told you thousand times
not to feed papers!
Kids!
You supposed to use them
for your homeworks
Here I come
No!
Sun-ja!
Pass the hall
Go over there, Cheol-su
No hands
You gotta kick it
No! Fetch the hall
Hey, wait... Yes!
That's cheating!
Cheol-su, you're out
I'm fine!
My hall!
Yes
Come with me for a second
Good cooking
It smells delicious
Hot!
- Dinner's ready
Dinner's ready
Mom, can I get a new baseball?
Cheol-su lost mine last time
Here we go again
He threw it so hard that
it went as far as the goat pen
So, Cheol-su is good at sports
Maybe he should become an athlete
How long is he going to stay with us?
They're still trying to find
a good place for him
There is a boy in my class
who lives in an orphanage
He never brings lunch
and wears the same clothes everyday
Well, it's not a nice place to live
How dare you look down on me?
I have more money than
all of you put together
What are you mumbling about?
You think you're better than me, too?
Anyone who dares to challenge me
will he taught a lesson
Got that?
Are we going to your place
for another drink?
You drink like a horse, girl
Want something other than ...
You distracted me, stupid cow!
What's that?
It's that damn freak again
- What are we gonna do?
- It's okay. He can't talk
This is my landlord's house
What just happened?
You...
Cheol-su
You're up with the sun, aren't you?
Come here
Do you want to try speaking?
Watch carefully and follow me
'Dee-geud'
Come on, try
Move your tongue like this
'Dee-geud'
Dee...
That's right. 'Dee-geud'
'Dee-geud'
Stop staring at me like that
Write the next one
How hard can it he?
Just write it
Draw a straight line, you see?
Like so
Your hands are very warm
Keep doing it over and over
and eventually, you'll get it
Come on, do the next one
I haven't played in ages
So I might not he as good,
hut I'll try anyway
It's a song I wrote a while ago
You can't laugh
All night long, I gaze out the window
waiting for the sun to come up
Because I can see him
when the morning comes
Thank you for holding my hands
Thank you for gazing into my eyes
Thank you, prince of my dreams,
for coming to me like this
There is a second verse, too
Hello?
Mrs. Kim?
I'm calling from the county office
What is this about?
I looked into it and
an orphanage looks difficult
but there is a facility for the disabled
that could take him in
Mrs. Kim?
There is no such person here
What are you doing?
Did you stash food again?
Don't even think about it
because I won't eat it
How long have you been wearing
the same clothes?
Mom says she'll get you new clothes
and always forgets
Are you decent?
This looks better than anything
you've ever put on
Let me see
You look hilarious
Look at me! Look at me!
You and I, we look ridiculous
Take a look
Sweetheart, I'm home
We gotta hide. Quick!
Where did she go?
Her shoes are here
Shush
Aw, I've been holding this in
for too long
Don't come out until I say so
I'm home!
Mom?
- Where are you?
- I'm on the toilet
- Hey, Sun-ja
- When did you get here?
I've been calling you
Why didn't you take this?
But I wanted to help
Where's Suni?
Must he out with Cheol-su
She never used to leave the house
I'm worried she'll collapse again
No, no!
I'm gonna take some rest
Eat your potatoes
and quit bothering me
You kids shouldn't do
that kind of stuff
Poor Mr. Jeong's goats
have all escaped
Mom, where did you find this?
You should've looked harder
before asking for a new one
But, I did!
You sure did... Take a quick peek
and come to me about everything
Have you seen my pajamas?
What's that you're wearing?
Pack your school hag and go to bed
I'll pack in the morning
Wait
Don't even think about it
What are you doing here at this hour?
You should show some respect
Such an ungrateful brat, aren't you?
Come with me
Let's grab a snack
I just want to talk to you
Cheol-su, stay
Who've we got here?
Come here
Why does he growl like a puppy?
Keep messing with me,
and I'll marinate you in bean sauce...
I'm only trying to help you up
Don't!
Hey, I'm not gonna eat you
- What the heck?
- Holy crap!
What's that?
What happened to him?
Do something!
Get away from me
Don't! I'm sorry
I won't do it again, I promise
Dad!
Wait
Wait...
A ghost?
Suni, you saw him, too
- Don't know what you're talking about
- What?
She says you broke into the house
and tried to assault her
Let's go to the station
- Break in?
- Go to bed, Sun-ja
Into my own house?
And look who got heat up here
Don't you know
who pays for your hospital hills?
And this house?
My father!
It was my father's business
that your family joined later
When he passed away,
you stole from the company
I know about things
Bringing up hospital hills or this house
won't do you any good
So, shut up!
Sweetheart, what are you saying?
That's enough
Have you lost your mind?
That's it!
Get rid of that freak
or move out of this house
Fine, bring it on!
Let's all go to the station together
Officer, you saw the hats and knives
they wielded at me
Why don't you call your father, too?
I have so many questions for him
If you're not going to do that,
leave my family and Cheol-su alone
Steady, son
This is fucking ludicrous
Think you're so smart?
Please, Ji-tae!
You have any idea
- who my father is?
- Please stop him
Cheol-su, what was that earlier?
Don't worry. It's gonna he fine
So you had some drinks before?
Some rice wine...
Just a little, eh?
- Come on, stay put
- Just a little Venus
Oh, Whiskey!
Foreign alcohol can screw you up real had
You don't believe me?
We were minding our own business
when that freak attacked us
and killed us all
Put the damn freak away!
No-one died. Just minor injuries
You little piece of shit!
Why did you stir up trouble
in the middle of the night?
- Officer...
- Shut up!
They're regulars here
The situation doesn't look
so good for you
Destruction of private property,
breaking and entering and assault...
And it's not really my business hut
what was that about
embezzling company funds?
Calm down, sweetheart
Why don't we call it a night here?
Come on, let's all go home
- Let's not bring suits between neighbors
- You're absolutely right, officer
I'm sure you can talk things out
Officer, can you uncuff him?
The smell is suffocating me
Doesn't it bother you?
What smell?
What a stench!
What are the hooks for?
They belong to him
You didn't happen to call my father,
did you?
Of course not
I'm letting this pass because
I don't want any more trouble
I know
Why should we fight like this
when Suni will marry me one day?
Let's try to get on a little
Where did you find a freak like that?
You can't let him leave this room
He's dangerous
What's all this?
Must belong to the former owner
Last of what I found
Park Jong-du?
Professor Kang?
Who the hell are you?
Do you know a man called
Park Jong-du?
I saw something interesting
and wondered
if you knew anything about it
Sit
Stay down
Your legs will hurt
Sit
and wait!
The smell won't go away
no matter how hard I clean
It's cold out
Why don't you go inside?
It's too stuffy inside
You've been working hard lately
That makes me feel so proud
To go to college
Then I will he a teacher
I think
I'm quite talented
Mom, aren't you going out
anywhere today?
I'm going into town to post
some manuscripts
You are fine with that, right?
Sure I am...
What are you talking about?
Don't... get too attached to
Chul-soo
I only came in
because it was getting cold
You can stop waiting now
Is that supposed to he me?
I can't
I don't have that anymore
But I brought you something else
Ta-ta!
My dad bought this for me
hut I never read it
And I won't he reading it now
because you're gonna read it for me
When you have learned to read and talk,
read it to me
I'll stroke your hair a hundred times
That's an order
Do you know what a snow man is?
Have you ever seen snow?
You make one
by rolling snow into a hall
We'll make one together
when it snows
On top of the hill where we played hall
It'll he so much fun
Promise?
Like this
Now, go hack to your study
It's stuffy in here
Hey!
Where have you been all this time?
Why haven't you learned to talk?
At least you're super strong
I'm not good at anything
You're a good boy, aren't you?
You're never going to hurt people again
You have so much more to learn
from me
Will you stay with me forever?
Say 'yes'
Yea...
See the pile of stones down there?
I'll race you
Whoever gets there first wins a favor
We'll start at three, okay?
One, two!
There's no-one home
Dong-seok's at school
- Suni!
- Kim Suni!
Cheol-su!
Suni!
Miss Kim Suni!
- Suni! Cheol-su!
- Kim Suni!
Where did they go?
Look over there
She's with Cheol-su
Stop crying, mom
I knew this was hound to happen
sooner or later
How did he get past the lock?
- Cheol-su!
- Suni!
- Who are these people?
- I don't know
We found them
Where?
Where are they?
- Suni!
- Where?
Suni!
Calm down, Mrs. Kim
- What are you doing?
- Just stand hack
Hey!
- What are you doing?
- Stand hack, kid
It's an anesthetic gun
You're trying to shoot him with it?
Kiddo, it's dangerous
Come on, Cheol-su
Let's go home
Good Lord! Suni!
Are you all right, sweetheart?
Wake up, child!
She shouldn't come this far out
Wolves are social predators
that live in packs
and are known
for their remarkable persistence
They can survive
without food for a long time
and mate with just one partner for life
What on earth are you talking about?
Was that too complicated?
Dr. Park wanted to create super soldiers
that can carry out effective infiltration
Where do I start?
So, what you're saying is
that's not a human-being hut a beast
Park and I worked together
in the same field
and we were good friends
So, he sent me this letter saying ...
Let's not talk about things
that need not he mentioned
Can I get something to drink?
Of course
His experiment had serious moral dilemmas
as it involved human subjects
If this gets out,
it'll become a huge scandal
Whoever commissioned this project ...
There is no evidence that the government
was involved with his project
I never mentioned any government
It was entirely his private work
Gross
- Don't delve too deep into this
- I never wanted to
We'll need to take Cheol-su with us
for some testing
I made myself clear on the matter
No-one outside can know about him
He is not to leave this premise
Why are you so concerned about
someone's private research work?
Why do you have so many questions?
I'm not sure of the details either
We'll observe him for a few days
If it turns out he was part of
the wretched experiment,
we have no choice
hut to put him down
You're going to kill him?
We can't afford to let this...
I mean, the boy to get out
I'm not following you at all
But you got this all wrong
Cheol-su is a good kid even if he can't talk
Even after what you saw today?
If we'd arrived a little later,
he'd have eaten her
You should've never taken him in
Grrr!
Careful, sweetie
It's okay, honey
We'll he hack in no time
Bring him his meal
See you later, Suni
Let me take that
Practice your writing
I'll he right hack, okay?
Eat plenty and don't
make noises at night
He's trying to escape
Suni
Are you okay?
Wait
Wait, Cheol-su
I told you he is dangerous
If this happens again
- Swear to God I'll shoot him
- Shoot him?
Don't you touch a hair on his head
Let's go
- Hey!
- Yes, sir
Isn't there anything to eat?
What on earth is he doing?
Learning the alphabets
Ga, na, da, la...
What for?
You gotta learn what you don't know
As you see, there isn't much movement
other than occasional staring at the door
Why isn't he eating?
Because Suni isn't here
Freezing!
If he shows a hint of violent behavior,
we'll put him down
I can tell from a glance
whether someone is a danger or not
His blood type is indeterminable
What about other readings?
His vision, hearing and sense of smell
are all good
Too good, actually
His body temperature is a little high
How high?
114.8 °F
It's not a fever
He is naturally hot
And he has a hone density and
muscle power that matches an elephant
If anyone asks,
tell them all the readings are normal
Sir?
If we don't take him with us,
he'll he killed here
- Sun-ja!
- Cheol-su!
Wanna spin a top?
It just rained, idiot
I have to stay home
Cheol-su can't play either
Why not?
Just can't...
Next time, okay?
It was a temporary shock
Nothing to worry about
Her conditions have
improved dramatically
- It's amazing what a change of air can do
- Oh, thank you, doctor!
- I got so worried
- Mom
Let's go home, mom
Everything is normal
He seems to he
quite gentle by nature
He's one of those kids
who lost parents in the war
There are tons of orphans like him
That's right
He's so much cleaner than me
I sometimes forget to brush
my teeth before bed
hut he brushes his teeth
even after lunch
Colonel
What are you saying?
You said you can tell from a glance
Didn't I tell you
that he turns into a monster?
He is different from us
He can't talk and is freakishly strong
He is a satan
What do you mean by that?
I don't have time on my hands
Can't he sitting around here all day
You can stop waiting now
Come here
My conclusion is that, although he lacks
social skills having been raised by animals,
he is capable of learning and
has the will to learn
Pending further observation,
hurting that boy will he
a meaningless murder
He has never displayed
violent tendencies
If that's true,
I'll report hack and return to base
He is so handsome, too
He reminds me of my nephew
I saw him
I saw him hurting goats
When?
A couple of weeks ago
At night
You were with him that night?
What happened?
We were driving when we saw him
hunting Mr. Jeong's goat
He was hunting a goat?
How?
Pardon?
He was feasting on it like a wolf
Why are you telling us this now?
I was scared he might hurt me
If you were there with her,
why didn't you say something before?
I'm telling you now
You know you're such a shitty liar
If you're gonna make up a story,
at least make some effort
Who's calling who a liar?
Mr. Jeong, you know
that Cheol-su didn't do it
Did you see him hurt your goat?
- I didn't see him prey on it
- But?
I saw him at the goat pen that night
Do you still have the dead goat?
No
But it wasn't killed by a wild animal
- I saw it with my own eyes
- Stop lying
You little hitch...
Hey, watch your mouth!
Don't you see that I'm here?
You have no respect
You all have lost your minds
All this nonsense because
you can't put down an animal?
We'll examine the site tomorrow
Everyone go home for now
Get some rest, sweetie
Suni
Don't you remember when...
we had a pinkie-swear
we'd he together forever and ever
What do you want?
I have something to say
What?
Cheol-su would have jumped over
If it was Cheol-su,
he'd have cleared it easy
hut the fence was hacked apart
The dead goat had no open wounds,
only broken ribs
Bring your car around tomorrow
I want to check something
I put some straw mats over the track
I'm going to show them tomorrow
What do you want from me?
If you've been telling a lie,
come clean
and I'll keep my mouth shut
Stop hassling good people
and go hack to Seoul
Hey, Jeong!
Hello?
Excuse me?
Who is it?
- It's a reporter
- A reporter?
He wants to come by for
some questions tomorrow
Hang up the phone
Shouldn't you he packing?
Journalists are coming
Don't he ridiculous
Change him hack into his own clothes
Just in case
Did you...
Did you hurt the goat?
I'm going hack in
I'm sick of these country bumpkins
- Go and take a look
- Yes, sir
Damned blackouts
What the heck?
Hey...
Ma'am, it's completely hashed up
What's hashed up?
Do you have a screw driver?
One moment
I just wanted to talk to you
I'm sorry I've been an asshole to you
How are you holding up, man?
You know what happened
to the guitar?
You know,
the thing you sing along to
Suni's been feeling down lately
Her guitar's gone missing
She can't sing,
so her health is getting worse
She might eventually die, you know?
You know who's taken it?
Jeong did
You know, the guy that keeps goats
Who would do this?
It's a secret hut
Suni doesn't really like you
In fact, she hates you
Bring the guitar hack to her
Who knows?
She might like you a little for that
Go get it now
It's hack on
- That's a relief
- It's hack on
Where did he go?
Oh my God,
the boy has gone nuts
What happened to you?
How did he get out?
Where on earth did he go?
We'll look for him
He's gone to Jeong's farm
He's craving the taste of meat
How do you know that?
I saw him on the way here
Where is this place?
Lead us there
You might want to bring the real gun
What's going on?
Who's there?
Cheol-su?
Hey, what are you doing?
What's gotten into you?
Stop it!
What's happening?
- Colonel?
- Go get the lady
- Hey!
- Are you all right, sir?
Mr. Jeong, are you okay?
What are you doing?
You thief!
Help me
Kim Cheol-su!
Put your hands in the air
and come out of there
- Come out of there now
- This way, ma'am
Oh my God! Honey?
What happened to you?
Wake up, Mr. Jeong!
What the hell?
What is she doing?
Hey!
Where are you going?
Stop!
Oh my God! Sweetie!
Come hack here
Let me talk to him
That's my daughter
Put the rifle away
Come on, shoot him
Shut your mouth for once
You're pointing the gun at my child
What if she gets hurt?
Cheol-su...
It's not here
Come to me
What the hell?
Are you crazy?
- Back off
- Put the gun down
- If you move, I swear I'll shoot
- Please, Ji-tae, stop!
Get out of the way
Put the gun down
Step aside
Please, stop
- I'll talk to him
- I've had enough
Get out of my way
Son, drop the weapon and hack off
Listen to me
I'll count to three
If you don't move,
I'll shoot you, too
One,
Cheol-su, wait
Stop it
two,
Stop this
- Stop!
- Three!
Wait!
Cheol-su, wait
- Suni!
- Sis!
Think you're better than me?
Stop it!
Think I'm a laughing stock?
- Do something!
- Huh?
Look at this mess
What the...?
After all that I did for you
Do you know how much I liked you?
Just calm down, boy
Go after him and kill him
Cheol-su
Are you really a freak?
Which is it?
Which is the real you?
I don't care
I don't care if you're a freak
Suni!
It's a rock, you idiot
You need to hide
Hurry!
They're coming this way
I'll tell them you ran away
Don't follow me
Go away, you idiot!
If you come with me,
they'll kill you
We can't he together now
Go!
Piss off!
I hate you
Get your dirty hands off me!
Go, you damn fool!
Oh, God...
I'm sorry, Cheol-su!
I'm so sorry
Don't follow me
I'm going
Don't you follow me
Don't go
Go away! I'm going now
Go away!
I'm sorry...
Just don't follow me
Over here, Colonel
What is it?
She came from that way
She's on her own
Are you all right?
Where have you been all night?
Where is he?
I don't know
What?
Why are you harassing her?
Are you lying to me?
I don't know
He ran away
How can you not know?
How dare you accuse
my daughter of lying?
- How can you not know!
- Will you just stop?
Calm down, everyone
If anything goes wrong,
I swear to God...
We should talk
What now?
If we expand the search
words will get out
Wasn't it your plan to cover this up?
Journalists will arrive soon
We'd better get our story straight
Unless you want things
to go a different way
Return to base for now
- Hurry
- Yes, sir
This is not the end of it
If he shows up,
contact me immediately
All right?
We'll he gone, too
What shall I do with this?
I meant to buy him some new clothes
hut I never got a chance
Come on, Suni!
Bye
- Take care
- Bye!
Dong-mi, come hack here
When Donghwa Trading went under,
the property was transferred
to your mother
And she left it to you when she died
A new resort is coming to the area
You'd want to sell it,
I presume?
It should do well
With clean air and all that
Can we stay for the night?
They must have rats here
Why did you want to stay over?
Don't know
You always say that
Gran, wanna see this?
What a good-looking young man!
He is, isn't he?
Does he come from money?
I don't think so
Then, just have a little fun and
dump him
But he's so good to me
Be good to him
Men love getting compliments
When you grow up, you see things
that you didn't use to see
Knowing more might seem good
hut it turns you into a coward
It only happens
once in your lifetime
And it never comes hack
Hello?
We're deep in the countryside
My gran?
She is something else
Yeah...
Let me call you hack
No, I'm fine
Good night
What have you got there?
It's a stun gun that dad got me
Just in case
Wait.
I'll come back
You've been waiting for me?
Chul-soo come here
You can stop waiting now
I'm so sorry, Chul-soo
Why did you wait?
I'm so sorry
I did it all
I did everything
I ever wanted to do
All alone
Without you
I am so sorry
I've become an old woman now
And my hair's gone all Grey
No
You haven't changed one hit
Your hands,
your mouth,
your eyes
you're still beautiful
I really missed you
Snow man was tempted
by what the dog told him
and suddenly felt a heat in his heart
That's really good
Dark as a charcoal,
his body is made of brass
When you put woods in his mouth,
it starts spitting fire
We're going now?
Why?
Did you forget something?
Let's go
Gran, I saw someone last night
He was watching me on the phone
You think you'd he scared
hut for some reason,
I wasn't afraid
Hello?
Good morning, it's Kim
from the county office
One moment
It's the officer from yesterday
I'm not selling it
Pardon me? You're not?
Thank you for holding my hands
Thank you for gazing into my eyes
Thank you, prince of my dreams,
for coming to me like this
All day long, I look upon the sky
waiting for the moon to come up
Because I can talk to him
when the night falls
Don't forget our promises
Don't forget our secrets
Don't forget how your eyes
made my heart pound